<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biomechanics on B. Yu</title>
    <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biomechanics on B. Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PCA for Gait Kinematics Time Series</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The traditional method to extract the meaning information from periodic gait cycle data is to simply find the maximum or minimum value of kinematic time series data. Yet maximum or minimum value is independent of time so that lots of information inside of the gait time series data are left behind. In this article, I will use PCA to overcome this drawback.
   Walking kinematics Times Series   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 0: The Test</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any question regarding my articles or my analysis project, or you have some feedbacks, please use the following contact form to send me the message. Please leave you email and question, and I will get back to use ASAP.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
