<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on B. Yu</title>
    <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on B. Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Biomechanics Data: Wide to Long </title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>This short article discuss how to turn &amp;ldquo;Wide&amp;rdquo; data into &amp;ldquo;Long&amp;rdquo; data. &amp;ldquo;Wide&amp;rdquo; data is very common in biomechanics studies. Investigators often measure many different variables(e.g., knee flexion/extension, COM, GRF&amp;hellip;), those variables are arranged in column. &amp;ldquo;Wide&amp;rdquo; data format is easy to understand, but difficult to be handled if you when to plot the data. So, you will need the &amp;ldquo;Long&amp;rdquo; data.
Experimental scenario: I am interested in examine how the two types of footwear affect the the lower limb coordination during running at 3 different speed: slow, normal and fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCA for Gait Kinematics Time Series</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The traditional method to extract the meaning information from periodic gait cycle data is to simply find the maximum or minimum value of kinematic time series data. Yet maximum or minimum value is independent of time so that lots of information inside of the gait time series data are left behind. In this article, I will use PCA to overcome this drawback.
   Walking kinematics Times Series   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daxiong2009.github.io/yu_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
